我们什么时候比一场
When we gonna spar?
我不喜欢你这种眼神
I don't like that look in your eye.
不  你做得很好
Nah, you're doing great--
每次出右拳的时候
Just keep dropping your left
记得把左手放下来  这样有意思
every time you throw your right cross, it'll be fun.
博伊特干净吗
Is Voight dirty?
又不是我的部门
It's not my department.
你这是肯定回答喽
So that's a yes.
我在缉捕队的时候差点完蛋
I almost went down the tubes when I was in vice,
从那时起我就不对其他警察做评论了
which was right around the time I stopped judging other cops.
我不是让你评论谁  我只想知道他这个人
I'm not looking for judgment, just a definition.
我是要向他学习  还是敬而远之
Do I learn from him, or do I keep my distance?
两者皆要
Both.
但如果你真想知道他干不干净  问她好了
But if you really wanna know if he's dirty or not, ask her.
爵士健美操好抢手啊
Jazzercise is, like, a block south.
你无袖T恤也不错
Yeah, nice muscle tee.
这个在拳击馆穿再合适不过了
This is perfectly acceptable attire for the boxing gym.
谁说不是呢
No, absolutely,
而且一会儿你跳霹雳舞的时候
and the bonus is you don't have to change later
还不用换衣服
when you break-dance.
-那是博伊特的儿子  -贾斯汀
- Voight's kid. - Justin.
这是安东尼奥和杰  我们是同事
This is Antonio and Jay. I work with them.
这家健身房是安东尼奥的哥们开的
Antonio's buddy owns the gym,
所以我们来可以打七折
hence the 30% discount.
-八折好吗  真会瞎掰  -好吧
- 20%. Nice try. - All right.
你好
How you doing?
我去打几个电话
I gotta make some calls.
他就跟我弟弟一样
He's like my little brother.
我只是不想让他惹麻烦
I'm just trying to keep him out of trouble.
祝好运
Good luck.
给他次机会
Just give him a shot.
这几个家伙被我撞到在街角卖毒品
Popped these guys selling off the corner.
那个大块头的莫里斯·欧文斯
Big guy, Maurice Owens,
说打电话找你
said to call you.
哥们  那些毒品是他们栽赃我的
Man, they planted that dope on me.
闭嘴
Shut up.
帮我手下的人也蒙混过去吧
I'm gonna need my boys to take a slide on this too.
我又不认识他们
I don't know these guys from a load of wood.
他们只能靠自己了
They're on their own.
-把莫里斯放了  -凭什么
- You can cut Maurice loose. - Based on?
就凭我一句话
Based on me saying you can cut him loose.
那我怎么跟上面说...
What am I gonna tell--
你怎么说是你的事
I don't care what you tell 'em.
把他放了
Uncuff him.
不在报告中提到他就是了
Write him out of your report.
我会把你们保释出来的  不用担心
I'ma bail y'all out. Don't worry.
-好  -行  快点
- Yeah. - Come on, do it.
我说过我的人会搞定...
I told you my boy would take care--
-是我不好  -和他说
- My bad. - Tell him.
我的错
My bad.
两千块
2 grand.
我大老远跑来可不是就为了两千块钱
Man, I didn't come across town for no 2 grand.
本来是五千的
Well, it was gonna be 5
可你在我的人面前揍了我
till you chumped me in front of my crew.
我可不是花钱买耻辱的
I don't pay you to get disrespected.
知道吗
Know that.
你想跟我闹矛盾吗  莫里斯
You wanna go toe-to-toe with me, Maurice?
午夜之前
I'll have 5 grand in my mitt
乖乖在我的拳击手套里放五千块
by the end of the night,
否则你就死定了
or the ground is gonna open underneath you.
贾斯汀怎么看起来一副苦大仇深的样子
All I'm saying is Justin looks like an uphill battle.
那个孩子失去了母亲  又在监狱待了一年
That kid lost his mother and then did a year in prison.
他只是需要重拾信心而已
He just needs to get his bearings.
你没看到在健身房他对我的态度吗
Did you see the attitude he gave me in the gym?
如果是我刚从监狱出来
If I had just gotten out of Statesville
然后还得跟一群警察握手
and had been made to shake hands with a bunch of cops,
我也会是那个态度的
I would've had the exact same attitude.
我觉得倒不是因为我是个警察
I don't think it's so much I'm a cop
更主要是因为他以为我是你男朋友
as much as Justin thinks I'm your boyfriend.
-想得美  -你想得美
- You wish. - You wish.
你才想得美
No, you wish.
-拜拜  -拜
- Hey. - Bye.
下班后见
I'll see you after work, okay?
对了  亚当
Oh. Hey, Adam.
-怎么了  -给你午餐
- Yeah? - Lunch.
对  我怎么会忘记这个呢
Right. How could I possibly forget?
不要忘记今晚一起吃晚餐
Don't forget about dinner tonight.
宝贝儿  我父母在我高中毕业后
Baby, my parents haven't been in the same room
就没共处一室过了
since my high school graduation.
我觉得他们还是抽签...
I really think that they should draw straws--
他们两个都应该去参加婚礼
They should both be at the wedding.
答应我  一定到场
Promise me you'll be there.
你是温迪吗
Are you Wendy?
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hey.
我是埃尔文
Alvin.
亚当的搭档
Adam's partner.
亚当怎么没跟我说过他有搭档
Adam didn't tell me he had a partner.
好  很好
Good, good.
他是按规矩行事
He's following protocol.
那好
Okay.
我们下班后见
I will see you after work.
再见
All right.
埃尔  我跟你说  她快用
Al, I'm telling you, she's killing me
那些婚礼计划搞死我了  她不明白
with this wedding planning, and she does not understand
让我父母一个桌上吃饭
that making my parents eat together,
无异于鲁塞克家的末日啊
it's the Ruzek nuclear option.
光是选什么瓷器还有记录保管就够受的了
Just china patterns and registries.
真是噩梦啊
This is gonna be a nightmare.
你说完了吗
Hey, are you through?
这里是我们工作的地方
Because when you're here, you're here.
你自己的事搞定了再进那扇门
So don't pass through that gate until you are.
知道了
Okay.
上面奖励了我们区一辆新巡逻车
The district's been awarded a new patrol car.
垃圾囤积那个案子你们两个干得不错
And since you guys went above and beyond on that hoarder deal,
所以新车就给你们用吧
I'm assigning it to you.
车在20英里外的地方
It's got 20 miles.
车刚出厂  你们还可以好好爽一把
You can still get high off the factory fumes.
我听说那批新车足足有400马力
I heard those new ones got, like, 400 horsepower in 'em.
你们听好
You listen up.
佩里长官想在下周的儿童玩具大巡游中
Commander Perry is going to drive it as a show car
把那辆车当做展示车辆
in next week's toys for tots parade.
要是刮伤了车的话
You bring it back with so much as a scratch,
他肯定会拿你们是问的  明白了吗
you're gonna have to answer to him--you hear me?
-明白  -明白
- Yes, ma'am. - Yes.
谢谢
Thank you.
-棒吧  -这辆车比我的房子还棒
- Yeah. - I mean, this thing is nicer than my apartment.
感受一下这个  来了哦
Oh, watch this, here it is.
这就是400马力的车  姑娘
Yeah. That's 400 horses, girl.
真不是闹着玩儿的
I ain't playin'.
你看到没有
Do you see that?
鸣警笛
Hit the lights.
这个姑娘需要帮助
This girl needs help, please.
小姐  你没事吧
Miss, are you okay?
2113号巡逻车报告  我们遇到一名精神病人
This is beat 2113--we got a disturbance with a mental.
女士们   你们...
Ladies, I need you to-- -
这是搞什么
What the hell was that?
什么情况
What do we got?
白人女性  刚做完手术
Female, white, just got out of surgery.
听说你被白人妞儿打得落花流水
I heard female white knocked you around pretty good.
她嗑的药让她比十个男人都有力气
Whatever she was on gave her the strength of ten men.
没发现身份证
No I.D.
她身上只有一张飞机票
All she had on her was this plane ticket.
她今早从墨西哥卡伯圣卢卡斯飞抵奥哈拉机场
She landed at O'hare this morning from Cabo San Lucas.
直说她带了多少可卡因吧
Just how much cocaine does she have on her?
不是带着的  都在她肚子里
Not on her. Inside her.
她的胃里有三十个安全套
30 balloons in her stomach.
通常情况下  警察带磕嗨的人过来
Normally, when cops drag screamers in here,
我们会给他们打一针镇静剂
we just give 'em a haldol cocktail
然后送去戒瘾所  但她却开始抽搐
and send them into detox, but she started convulsing,
我立刻发觉她的情况不对
and I knew right away this was different.
欢迎来到芝加哥
Welcome to Chicago,
中西部毒品集散中心
distribution center of the Midwest.
我们取出了29个装满可卡因的安全套
We removed 29 condoms full of cocaine,
而她吞下了30个
though she swallowed 30.
有一个破裂了  里面的可卡因被她的胃吸收
One broke open and started to dissolve into her stomach.
毒品渗入她的血液循环
The drug leaked into her bloodstream,
导致她精神错乱  所以我进行了紧急手术
causing her psychosis, so I ordered emergency surgery.
人为了钱能做出的事总让我叹为观止
Never ceases to amaze me what people will do for money.
其实有时候  他们只是别无选择
Well, sometimes, people don't feel like they have a choice.
我检测了破裂安全套中的残留物
I tested the residue on the broken balloon.
纯度高达百分之八十九
It's 89% pure.
是我见过的最高的
That's the highest grade I've ever seen.
这些东西起码市值五万
All these must be 50k street value.
-只多不少  -那这是怎么回事
- Easy. - So what do we think?
贩毒集团开始雇佣正宗美国人了吗
Cartel's getting smart recruiting all-American types?
这里面都是气泡
They're full of air pockets.
所以才会破裂  这是生手所为
That's why they busted. It's amateur hour.
贩毒集团的人不会这么粗心大意
Cartel wouldn't be this careless.
我们得直接审讯她  她过多久会醒
We need to question her. How soon till she's conscious?
两到三个小时吧
Two, maybe three hours.
让吉恩联系奥哈拉机场的运输安全管理局
All right, have Jin contact the TSA at O'hare.
看看能不能查到这个女孩的身份
See if we can get an I.D. on this girl.
这下完了
We're so screwed.
没错
Yep.
普拉特会气疯的
Platt's gonna freak.
我们得把它开回警署车库去
We have to take it to the police garage.
不行  警署车库补个胎都要一个月
No, the police garage takes a month to fix a flat.
可是儿童玩具大巡游这周末就要举办了
The toys for tots parade is this weekend.
我有个更好的主意
I got a better idea.
好吧
All right.
怎么回事
What's up?
刮掉了很多漆啊  老兄
I see y'all got a lot of paint damage, man.
这儿还有块凹陷
Got a hell of a dent right here.
外加这个彻底坏了的反光镜
This busted side mirror.
得给我两天时间才能修好  阿特沃特
You're gonna give me two days on this, Atwater.
抓紧点儿怎么样
Eh, I'm thinking a lot sooner,
比如在我下班之前修好
like by the end of this shift.
老兄  你来这要当天取车服务
Bro, you came here for the same-day service?
那可是很贵的
You know that's gonna cost you, right?
我可以给你一张富乐客鞋店的三百块礼品卡
I got $300 of Foot Locker gift cards for you.
明天再给你一百
I can get another 100 by tomorrow.
开什么玩笑  老兄  不行
Come on, man. Nah.
这又不是旧货交换市场
It's not a swap meet, okay?
你让我修的可是警车  老兄
You ask me to fix a cop car, bro.
一口价  现金五百块
$500 cash, or no deal.
-成交  -好的  老兄
- Make it happen, man. - All right, man.
-好的  -我办事你放心
- All right. - Yeah, you know I got you.
好了  小伙子们  我们又有活儿了
All right, boys, we got another one.
-你有多少钱  -什么
- How much you got? - What?
不知道  大概十八块吧
I don't know, like-- like, $18.
我们得找台自动取款机  卡尔不收支票
We need to hit an ATM 'cause Carl don't take checks.
在周五发工资之前
I don't have 250 bucks,
我可拿不出二百五十块
not until we get paid Friday.
那就打电话找人借呗
Get on the horn and borrow it then.
航班旅客名单显示
According to the flight manifest,
你们要查的女孩名叫安柏·莫里斯
your girl's name is Amber Morris.
乘坐卡伯圣卢卡斯的夜班机  今早抵达
Came in on the red-eye from Cabo San Lucas this morning.
她有同行者吗
Was she traveling with anyone?
问得好
Great question.
-能先等我说完吗  -抱歉
- Can I finish? - Sorry.
安柏的信用卡一共买了四张票
Four tickets total were purchased on Amber's credit card.
看这里
And here they are,
是她和她的朋友下飞机的录像
her and her friends getting off the plane.
你觉得这些女孩都是运毒犯吗
You think all those girls are mules?
芝加哥中央大学
被通缉
戴维斯
无前科
在急诊室的女孩名叫安柏·莫里斯
All right, so our girl in the E.R. is Amber Morris.
未监护
莫里斯
无前科
芝加哥医院
安柏和她的三个朋友都是
Amber and her three friends here are all undergrads
芝加哥中央大学的在校生
at Central Chicago University.
这就是我们要找的人
This is who we're looking for.
我们查过安柏的脸谱网主页
We checked Amber's Facebook page.
里面有他们在卡伯狂欢的照片
There's pictures of them living it up in Cabo,
不仅仅是这次
but not just from this trip.
安柏在过去三个月里共去了两次
Amber's been down there twice in the last three months.
第一次  她一个人去
First time, she did the run herself.
这次  她带上了朋友
This time, she recruited friends.
我们得假定这些女孩都是运毒犯
We gotta assume all these girls are mules
吞下了同样的装有可卡因的安全套
and ingested the same type of balloons packed with coke.
各位  我查到了那些女孩的住处
You guys, I ran down those girls' addresses.
三个都住在学校里
All three live on campus.
行动
We gotta move.
我们走
Let's go.
要是你还想继续在这工作  就给我收敛点
You like working in this unit, you keep it in your pants.
我又不收敛吗
I didn't know it was out.
艾琳碰不得
Erin's off-limits.
言尽于此
End of discussion.
-你好  -警长
- Hey. - Sergeant.
莎拉·海恩斯  芝加哥警署
Sarah Hines. Chicago PD.
她来过宿舍
Well, she made it home.
梅根
Megan.
梅根·班森
Megan Benson.
艾莉莎·戴维斯
Alicia Davis?
救命
Help.
-你是谁  -我叫雪莉·贝茨
- Who are you? - I'm Shelly Bates.
-我是宿舍管理员  -是艾莉莎打伤你吗
- I'm an R.A. - Alicia do this to you?
不  是两个男人
No, two guys.
他们带走了她
They took her.
她病的很重  所以我想帮忙照顾她
She was really sick. I tried to help.
我们要找两名白人男性
We're looking for two white males.
可能还在附近  他们带走了我们要找的人
Could still be in the area. They got our girls.
好的  汉克  一有那辆车的消息就通知我们
All right, Hank, just keep us posted on the van.
我们搞砸了  那些女孩又不知所踪了
So messed up--these girls out there with no idea.
是啊
Yeah.
等案子办完了  我得去喝一杯
I'm gonna need a drink when this is done.
你觉得呢
What do you say?
你老爸可不会喜欢你这么做
Oh, I don't think your dad would like that.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你觉得我说的是什么
What do you think I'm talking about?
她醒了  你们可以去看她了
She's awake now. You can come and see her.
难以置信我竟然在这里
I can't believe I'm in here.
醒醒吧  安柏
Believe it, Amber,
你为之卖命运毒的人
and whoever you were smuggling for
刚刚绑架了你的朋友
just kidnapped your friends.
如果你不交代谁是幕后主谋
So if you don't give up who's behind this
一旦我们发现你朋友死了
and we find your friends dead,
你就将一个人全部扛下
you're gonna be facing narcotics-induced homicide
涉毒谋杀的罪名
all by your lonesome.
-我不能说  -你没听到我们的话吗
- I can't. - Are you listening?
我们发现你是你走运
You're lucky we found you.
现在你只不过会在肚子上留下一道疤
Now, all you're gonna have is a scar on your stomach,
但是你的朋友很有可能会因吸毒过量
but your friends, they'll likely O.D.
而死在某条小巷里
and wind up in some alley.
如果事情变成那样  你觉得
And if that happens, I promise you
永远都不会原谅自己的
you will never forgive yourself.
你得帮我们救出她们  安柏
You need to help us save them, Amber.
我爱他
I loved him.
宝贝  利用你干这种事的男人
Sweetheart, the guy that used you for this...
绝对是不爱你的
He doesn't love you.
我以前干过一次  那次没事
I did it once, and it was fine.
然后他答应我的朋友们每次五千元
Then he promised my friends 5 grand each to go.
是我男朋友的主意
It was my boyfriend's idea,
他和他兄弟
him and his brother.
我们要发布一个调查警报
We're putting out an investigative alert
追查肖恩和布兰登·柯林斯
on a Sean and Brendan Collins.
他们是我们要找的毒贩
They're the dealers we're looking for.
肖恩是她男朋友  安柏说他和他兄弟
Sean's the boyfriend. Amber says him and his brother,
在一家叫"地下墨水"的纹身店出没
they hang out at a tattoo shop called "Underground Ink".
他们就在那卖货
That's where they sling the product.
-干得好  -我去让奥林斯基和鲁塞克
- Good work. - I'll get Olinsky and Ruzek
去监视这家纹身店
to set up on this tattoo shop.
不  那里面全是碳水化合物和糖
No, those are loaded with carbs and sugar, man.
但是对人体有益
But they're good carbs.
不  不  盯梢入门第一课
No, no, stakeout 101.
你必须吃纯天然全蛋白质食品
You gotta go all-natural, all-protein.
太多碳水化合物会让你疲劳  注意力不集中
Too much carbs leave you tired and unfocused.
摄入碳水化合物会引起血清素升高而犯困
餐后犯困是大忌
You don't wanna be in a carbohydrate coma.
所以才要准备这些提神啊  埃尔
That's what these are for, Al.
巡警已经确认柯林斯兄弟
So patrol already confirmed that the Collins brothers
不在纹身店里
aren't at this tattoo parlor.
为什么我们还要监视那里
Why do we got to babysit it?
我们就是干这个的
That's what they pay us for.
-好吧  -你多大号
- Yeah. - You're what?
-你32号  -是啊
- You're 32? - Mm-hmm.
等等  等等  这些是干什么的
Wait, wait, wait. What are those for?
这次盯梢不知道要多长时间
You're on a stakeout for who knows how long
还要喝那些色素饮料
drinking that fluorescent poison...
你是憋不住的
You're not gonna be able to hold it.
你开玩笑吧
You can't be serious.
我会找地方撒尿的
I'll find somewhere to take a leak.
我还是新手的时候
You know, when I was a rookie,
曾被派去监视一个入室盗窃团伙
I was assigned to keep eyes on this B&E crew
-他们很难抓  -然后呢
- that nobody could touch. - Right.
我第一次看到他的时候让他跑了
The first time I got eyes on him, I lost him.
-你知道为什么吗  -不
- You know why? - No.
因为我去撒尿了
'Cause I had to take a piss.
我最多走开了三四分钟
And I'm gone three, four minutes tops.
所以我告诉自己  下次看到他的时候
And I say to myself, "Next time I got eyes on him,
我会纹丝不动  哪也不去
I'm not gonna move. I'm not going anywhere."
所以这个就派上了用场
And that's where these came in.
然后我拿下了那个团伙  追回了一百万美元
And I nailed the crew pulling a million-dollar score.
明白了吗
All right?
在医院的那个女孩
The girl who's in the hospital,
安柏·莫里斯  她妈妈在楼下
Amber Morris, her mother's downstairs.
好的  带她上来
All right, bring her up.
我假设这句话的西班牙语意思是
I'm assuming that's Spanish
你会自己下楼去接待她
for "You're gonna go down there and get her yourself."
我女儿和这些没有任何关系
I'm telling you my daughter had nothing to do with this.
女士
Ma'am...
他们从你女儿胃里取出
They cut 30 condoms packed with cocaine
30个包裹着可卡因的安全套
out of your daughter's stomach.
我很肯定她和这些有关系
I'm pretty sure she had something to do with it.
一定是有人强迫她的
Someone must have forced her.
你应该去抓他们而不是我女儿
You need to go after them and not my daughter.
根据我们目前的调查
The way it looks so far
安柏干这个是自愿的
is Amber did this of her own free will.
不可能
That couldn't be.
安柏是个好学生
Amber was a good student.
她刚被评上了优秀学生
She just made the Dean's List.
她是为了钱才这么做的  莫里斯太太
She did this for money, Mrs. Morris.
我知道你很难接受
I know this is hard for you to hear.
也很难相信
Hard to believe.
但是孩子们去上大学
But kids go off to college.
离开父母
They get away from their parents.
有时难免会犯糊涂
Sometimes they get mixed up in bad things.
她会怎么样
What's gonna happen to her?
她一直很合作
She's been cooperative so far.
我们会和州检察官商量
We'll talk to the state's attorney,
尽量让她不用坐牢
try to keep her out of jail.
我也有一个女儿
I have a daughter.
十三岁
She's 13.
我也很担心她和朋友们
I worry about her with her friends,
和男孩子一起玩
with boys.
但你不可能时刻盯着她们
But you can't watch 'em every second.
至少安柏还活着
At least Amber's alive.
那些家伙不可能带着他们绑架的三个女孩
You know, there is no way these guys show up here
出现在这里
with three kidnapped girls.
罪犯会狗急跳墙  警察就得加班加点
Criminals get desperate, cops get overtime.
你急着下班吗
You in a hurry to punch out?
我今晚晚餐有约
Well, I got this dinner tonight.
我妈妈和继母  她们彼此看不顺眼
My mom and my stepmom, they hate each other,
所以我得确保她俩都来参加婚礼
so it's on me to make sure they both show up
但不会杀了对方
to the wedding and don't kill one another.
想想我会开心吗
Ask me if I'm excited.
别  埃尔  那是温迪  别挂断
Hey, Al, no, that's Wendy. Come on, don't clear it.
别挂断
Don't clear it.
好了吗
All right.
好吧
注意那里
Right there.
注意力集中在当前任务上
Focus on the task at hand.
好吧
All right.
柯林斯兄弟是布里奇波特市有名的罪犯
The Collins brothers are known thugs from Bridgeport.
两个人都有持械抢劫和
Both have records for armed robbery
恶性斗殴的案底
and aggravated battery.
然后他们发展到
So they've graduated to
利用无知女大学生运毒了
drug smuggling using naive college girls.
警察检查了他们的已知住处
Had uniforms check their LKAs.
这些家伙已经跑了
These guys are in the wind.
车管所说布兰登·柯林斯
DMV came back that Brendan Collins
有一辆黑色福特商务车
owns a black Ford van.
我猜这兄弟俩用的是一次性手机
I'm assuming that these brothers are using throwaway phones
因为他们知道安柏已经被捕了
now that they know Amber's been arrested.
好  继续查
All right, keep digging.
把他们的同伙都给我抓来
Get me any known associates.
我们得谈谈
Hey, we need to talk.
来吧
Come on.
怎么了
Yeah?
你这种严父行为在我十几岁时还可以
The overprotective father thing was fine when I was a teenager,
但现在我已经不需要你担心了
but I don't need you looking out for me anymore.
我担心的是霍斯特德
It's Halstead I'm looking out for.
我见过和你约会的男生的下场
I've seen what happens to the guys you date.
这是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
你从十五岁起
You've left a string of broken hearts
就不知道伤过多少男孩的心
behind you since you were 15.
我不想让霍斯特德分心
I need Halstead 100% effective,
不想让他半夜三点
not throwing pebbles
还在你窗外扔石子
at your window at 3:00 in the morning.
我在私人时间里和谁
You don't get to tell me who I can
去约会不是你能说了算的
and can't hang out with on my personal time.
我的地盘我做主  你想跟警察约会吗
My unit, my rules. You wanna date a cop?
别的局里有的是
There are plenty other districts out there.
刚找到布兰登·柯林斯的面包车
Hey, just got a ping on Brendan Collins' van.
-在哪里  -你还好吗
- Where? - Everything all right?
把地址发给我就行
Just send me the address.
好了  吉恩  施展你的魔法吧
All right, Jin, work your magic.
收到  等我来看看
Stand by. Let me get comfy.
看到面包车了吗
We got eyes on the van yet?
说了稍等
Said I'm getting comfy.
好了  看到他了
Okay, got eyes on 'em.
正在从76大街向西开
Comin' up 76th towards western.
拐进了一条小巷
Turning into an alley.
向南往77大街开
Heading south towards 77th.
收到
We're on it.
看到布兰登·柯林斯了
Got a visual on Brendan Collins.
车掉头了  在往北向76大街开
Van's on the move, headed north on 76th.
吉恩  你看到了没
Jin, you got it, or what?
看到了  他在向西往75大街开
Got him. He's goin' west on 75th.
-就是那辆车  -很好  我们围住他
- There's the van. - All right, let's box it in.
-先生  你还好吗  -没事
- Sir, are you okay? - I'm fine.
5020L  紧急情况
5020 Lincoln. Emergency.
西大街7320号需要一辆救护车
Roll an ambulance to 7320 Western.
收到  马上派出救护车
Copy that. Ambo on the way.
他死了
He's toast.
看看女孩们
The girls!
他身上有把枪和一部一次性手机
He had a 9 mil and a throwaway phone.
没有毒品和女孩的影子
No trace of the coke or the girls.
时间越久
So every second that goes by,
那些女孩们生还的可能性越小
the less chance those girls survive.
这谁都知道  艾琳
We're all aware of that, Erin.
大家都冷静
Everybody stay cool.
尽快把电话送给吉恩检查
Get that phone over to Jin ASAP.
让他查查上面的通话记录
Have him run the calls on it.
你跟我走
You're comin' with me.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
去会会他的家人去
Higher up the family tree.
你怎么能趴这么久的
How do you lay here this long?
我都快无聊死了
I'm bored out of my mind.
你训练好自己的大脑  身体就会跟上的
You train your mind, your body will follow.
好吧
Yeah, well,
我得去活动活动
I'm gonna go stretch my legs, all right?
亲爱的
Hey, baby.
-我怎么说的  -埃尔  别闹
- What'd I say? - Al, come on.
我就跟她说两句
I need to talk to her quick.
埃尔
Al.
-你玩儿我呢吧  -新手错误
- You gotta be kidding me. - Rookie mistake.
我不想再说第二遍了
I don't wanna have to say it again.
-你现在给我专心  -你到底是怎么回事
- You stay focused now. - What the hell's your problem?
给我滚回屋顶边上去
Just get your ass to the edge of that roof.
你得赔我个新的
You're buyin' me a new phone.
对  在拉瑞米和杰克逊大街的路口
Yeah, on the corner of-- of Laramie and Jackson.
对  是很偏西的地方
Yeah, it's the far west side.
对  我知道是贫民窟
Yes, I know it's the ghetto,
但你不会被抢的  凯特兰
but you're not gonna get robbed, Caitlan.
你开玩笑吗  我是警察啊
Are you kidding me? I'm a cop.
B2113号
Beat 2113.
-2113收到  -西坎齐大街3300号
- Go--go for 2113. - We have a store owner
有名店主在店内抓住了一名女小偷
holding a female shoplifter at 3300 West Kinzie.
离这里有十个街区远
That's ten blocks away.
店主说小偷正在威胁人群
Store owner says the woman is making threats
很可能携带武器
and could be armed.
明白  马上过去
10-4. We're en route.
把她给我抓起来
I want her arrested.
好的  球棒给我好吗  先生
All right, how about I take that bat, sir?
-您说她携带武器吗  -我不知道  看看她
- You said she was armed? - I don't know. Look at her.
一个瘾君子  说不定有武器呢
She's a crackhead. Figured she might have a weapon.
她想偷什么呢
What did she try to steal?
我抓到她想把这个藏衣服里
I caught her trying to put this under her coat.
女士
Ma'am.
您是想偷面包吗
Did you try and steal the bread?
我丈夫卖掉了我们的低保卡
My husband sold our link card,
我身上也没有钱
and I don't have any money.
我不吸毒
I'm not a drug addict.
只是想给我儿子做个三明治
I just wanted to make my boy a sandwich.
你到底要不要逮捕她
You gonna arrest her or what?
面包多少钱
How much is the bread?
1.5美元
$1.50.
不如您高抬贵手
How about we let it slide?
让她在这干点事抵掉面包钱...
Have her work it off helping you...
帮你打扫下什么的
clean up or something?
这个瘾君子想偷我东西
This junkie tried to rip me off.
干正事  把她抓起来
Do your job and lock her up,
否则我打电话喊真警察来了
or I'm gonna call some real police.
您想喊真警察是吗
You want the real police?
-他想喊真警察  -真警察
- He wants the real police. - The real police.
没问题  没问题  真警察来了
Okay, okay. Well, now you've got 'em.
那我们就按制度办事吧  怎么样
Let's follow this by the letter of the law, shall we?
-来吧  -阿特沃特
- Let's do it. - Atwater.
这些执照都在期限内吗
Do all those licenses look up to date?
香烟  乳制品和农产品
Cigarettes, dairy, produce?
请您稍微让下  先生
Uh, step aside for a second, sir.
让我来看看
Let me take this out.
你们的工资可都是从我交的税里来的
Hey, I pay my taxes that pays your salary.
她才是犯法的那个
She's the one who broke the law.
这些是鼠粪吗
Are those rat turds?
看起来像是鼠粪
Mm. It look like rat turds.
真的很像鼠粪啊
They do look like rat turds.
这绝对是违规
That's a definite violation.
再看看那个
And look at that.
故障线路  不符合规定
Faulty wires. That's against code.
您看  我已经发现了两千块左右的罚款项目
See, I see about $20,000 in fines so far.
带她从我店里出去
Just get her outta here.
来吧  女士  您没事了
Come on, ma'am. You're all right.
给您
Here you go.
老话说得好  "纳税人"先生
There's an old saying, Mr. Taxpayer.
虽然动嘴皮子躲不过罚单
You can't talk your way out of a ticket,
但绝对能让自己惹上麻烦
but you sure as hell can talk your way into one.
你偷溜出来见我  警官大人会生气吗
Is deputy dog pissed you're sneaking out to meet me?
谁  霍尔斯特德吗
Who, Halstead?
我觉得你俩之间有点小火花什么的
Figured you had a little thing with him or something.
有啊  不就是"工作"嘛
Yeah. It's called "Work."
随你说吧  你拿到了吗
Whatever. Did you get it?
你怎么没去上交管局的培训课
Why aren't you at the CTA training class?
因为我把钱包忘在了你车里
Because I left my wallet in your car,
没有身份证
and I don't have my I.D.
我重新排到了下周
I rescheduled it for next week.
贾斯汀
Justin.
你父亲托了很多关系
Your dad pulled a lot of strings
才帮你弄到这份工作的你知道吗
to get you this job, all right?
好歹去露个面吧
The least you could do is show up.
那我就得去上几天班  哄他开心吗
I'll punch in a little while, make him happy?
得了吧  艾琳  交管局有前途吗
Come on, Erin. CTA is not a career.
反正我还有别的事干
I got other things cookin', anyways.
-真的吗  -对
- Oh, really? - Mm-hmm.
那是等你的吗
Is that your ride?
别担心  他没事的
Don't worry about it. He's cool.
老朋友而已
Just an old friend.
好了 我过会儿给你短信
All right. I'll text you later.
也许你下班后我们可以出去逛逛
Maybe we'll hang out after work,
喝点小酒什么的
get some drinks or somethin'.
或者我应该把你顺便送回家
Or maybe I'll give you a ride home.
你知道你有宵禁的
You know you have curfew.
你帮我注意着点就行
Just watch my back.
加文·柯林斯
Gavin Collins.
汉克
Hank.
我们这一局还没打完呢
We're in the middle of a game.
那恭喜你了
Well, congratulations.
你赢了
You won.
今早  我还有两个侄子的
This morning, I had two nephews.
你有什么要解释的吗
You wanna explain that?
你侄子让小姑娘吞食可卡因
Your nephews use girls to swallow cocaine
然后从墨西哥运到这里来
and bring it up from Mexico.
布兰登和我们玩了一场高速追逐战
Brendan took us on a high-speed chase.
他是在自掘坟墓
He dug his own grave.
抱歉  我现在没时间和你谈
Sorry. I ain't got time to talk.
玩完这局我还得去看我妹妹伤心欲绝
After this, I gotta go see my sister grieve.
所以带上你那群大学吸毒的小妞们
So take your college junkie whores
赶紧的滚犊子吧
and shove 'em up your ass.
给我
Gimme that!
不要让他起来
Keep him down.
你侄子肖恩现在
Your nephew Sean is out there right now
绑架了三个姑娘在逃
with three kidnapped girls.
如果我不找到她们的话
Odds are they don't make it through the night
可能她们就活不过今晚了
if I don't find them.
他肯定藏在什么地方
He's got a stash out somewhere.
给你三秒钟告诉我地址
You got three seconds to give me the address,
否则我就一枪崩的你脑袋开花
or I'm gonna blow your brains all over the floor.
一
One.
二
Two.
警察
Police.
米德威半数的赃物肯定都藏在这里
Half the swag from Midway must be in here.
去后面看看
Check the back.
梅根·班森
Megan Benson.
那个女孩19岁  还在上学
Girl was 19. Still in school.
-真是可惜了  -为什么只有一个
- Now, what a waste. - Why do only one?
还有两个在哪里
Where's the other two?
这不是专业人员所为
We're not dealing with a pro.
柯林斯被吓跑了
Collins got squeamish and ran.
动刀的那个人把安全套切开了
Whoever cut into her cut into the condom balloons,
大部分可卡因都毁掉了
destroyed most the cocaine.
谢谢  医生
Thanks, doc.
柯林斯现在绝不敢
There's no way Collins can afford
对另外两个做同样的事
to do that to the other two.
我现在要去处理点别的事情
Look, I got some business to take care of.
问下吉恩有没有查到什么  好吗
See if Jin's got anything yet, all right?
你们从布兰登货车里找到的
I was able to obtain subscriber info
那部手机里的所有用户信息
for all calls from Brendan's cell phone
我都找到了
that you found in his van.
只有两个号码  一个是肖恩的预付费手机
Only two numbers, first to Sean's prepaid cell
这个手机已经被遗弃了
which has since gone dead,
但我还是追踪到它在阿什兰的一个垃圾堆里
but I was able to track it to a dumpster on Ashland.
第二个号码  六次打给了这个人
Second, six calls to this guy.
-赖安·波特  -赖安·波特
- Ryan Porter. - Ryan Porter.
白人男性  26岁  多次私藏毒品
Male, white, 26. Long sheet for possession.
在三个不同的
Worked as a paramedic
救护车公司做护理人员
for three different ambulance companies,
三个公司都开除了他
fired from all of them.
我知道了
I know that M.O.
波特十有八九在外面赚外快
Ten-to-one Porter's a play doctor.
我在缉捕队工作时抓到过几个
Busted a few when I worked vice.
急救医师是在私人救护车公司工作的
EMTs who work for private ambulance companies.
他们一小时赚不到十美元
They barely make 10 bucks an hour.
所以如果想赚外快的话
So the ones who wanna make extra cash
他们有时候会提供秘密服务
sometimes provide under-the-table services
比如救治少年罪犯之类的
like patching up gangbangers.
尽快将波特的照片传给奥林斯基
Forward Porter's picture to Olinsky asap.
比在你车里谈好多了
It's a step up from your car.
州检察官办公室
State's attorney office is having
今晚在宴会厅举办年会
their annual conference tonight in the banquet hall.
也有内务部的份
I.A. has a table.
你知道真正的警察是怎么说州检察官的吗
You know what the real police call the state's attorney?
就是专门管放人的
203 set 'em free.
你是说我们不算真正的警察吗
You sayin' we're not the real police?
麦克弗森
McPherson.
那份拘捕令好用吗
How'd that warrant work out for you?
我们听说你今天去找了加文·柯林斯
We heard you paid Gavin Collins a visit today,
你没有尊重他的米兰达权利
and you weren't that forthcoming with his miranda rights.
我们只是聊了聊而已
We just talked, that's all.
据缉捕队说
According to vice,
加文·柯林斯走私了好几车未完税的香烟
Gavin Collins brings in trucks full of untaxed cigarettes.
你要拿下他吗
You gonna bring him down?
今天没计划拿下他
That's not on today's agenda.
那你的计划是什么  博伊特
What is your agenda, Voight?
你应该给我们搞定那些主要参与者
You're supposed to be taking down major players for us,
结果你连莫里斯·欧文斯都搞不定吗
and you can't even bust Maurice Owens?
听着  警长
Listen, Sergeant,
你能够复职的唯一原因
the only reason you got your badge back
是你和内务部以及
is because of your arrangement with I.A.
州检察官办公室的约定
and the state's attorney's office.
你退缩了
You're going backwards.
这样下去  除非你能解决一些重案要案
At this rate, unless you get us some heavy case on paper,
否则你就完了
you're done.
我刚找到一个被取出内脏的姑娘
I just found a disemboweled girl.
还有两个姑娘可能会有相同的遭遇
I got two more out there that could end up the same.
如果你不介意的话  我要回去工作了
So if you don't mind, I'd like to get back to work.
如果你不践行我们的约定  你就回监狱里去
If you don't honor our deal, you are going back to prison.
我必须得说
Hey. I gotta say it.
-你真牛  伙计  -我知道
- You da man, dog. - Yeah, I know that, man.
来吧  你钱带齐了吗
Come on. Hey, you got my money?
是的
Yeah.
这是一半
Here's half of it.
还有一半在她那儿  兄弟
She's good for the other half, man.
发工资的时候我会把她带过来
I'll bring her back on payday.
你就是在A-1商店给桑德拉买面包的那个人吗
Are you the one that bought the bread for Sandra over at the A-1.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know that?
她是我铁哥们儿的妹妹
She's my homey's sister, man.
她去年失业了
You know, she lost her job last year.
老公游手好闲
Husband's a deadbeat.
她只是想好好照顾她的孩子而已
Just tryin' to do right by the kids, you know?
好吧  我给你打个折
All right, I'll hit you with a discount, yo.
我只收250  好吗
I'll just take the 250, all right?
没问题
No doubt.
行了  该手工了吧
All right. Well, I think they're closed.
我们该去做点别的了
Maybe it's time to move on to something else.
给我闭嘴趴好
Just lay down and shut up.
吉恩发了条警报信息来
Got an alert from Jin.
太好了  我也看看我的手机
That's great. I'll just check my phone.
对了
Oh, ho. That's right...
它从屋顶自由落体下去了
It took a nosedive off the roof.
趴下  趴下
Get down. Get down.
他带着一个医用包
He's got a medical bag.
对
Yep.
那就是我们的外快医生
That's our play doctor.
还有肖恩·柯林斯
And there's Sean Collins.
笑一笑吧  你个混蛋
Say "Cheese," You son of a bitch.
那就是我们要找的女孩  对吧
That's gotta be our girls, huh?
只有一种方法去查明了
Only one way to find out.
-跟你说过了  耐心点  -我知道
- Told you. Patience. - I know.
-我把他们叫来  -没问题
- I'll call it in. - You got it.
我是奥林斯基
Olinsky.
我们看见坏人了
We got eyes on the bad guys.
他们手里有那两个女孩
They have the two girls.
重复一遍  那两个女孩好像跟他们在一起
I repeat, looks like the two girls are with them.
去地下墨水纹身店支援  午餐时间结束
Underground Ink Tattoo shop, code seven.
我们到底要不要进去
We goin' in, or what?
队员们正往这边赶呢
Team's on its way.
鲁塞克  等待后援
Ruzek, wait for backup.
必须等待后援
You have to wait for backup!
该死
Damn it!
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
举起手来
Get your hands up!
把刀子放下  离她远一点
Drop that knife. Get away from her.
把手举起来  不许动
Put your hands up. Don't move!
-离她远一点  -不许动
- Back away from her. - Don't move!
不许看我  双手扶墙
Don't look at me! Hands on the wall!
柯林斯  趴下  快趴下
Collins, get down. Get down.
这里还有谁
Who else is in here, huh?
我们需要紧急救援  快点
We need emergency assistance. Now!
她流了太多血了
All right, we got a lot of blood here, man.
-你会没事的  -给你 给你
- You're okay. - Here, here.
让我看看  坚持住  我懂  我懂
Let me see. Hang in there. I know, I know.
马上就有人来帮你了  救护车已经在路上了
Help is coming. An ambulance is on the way.
阿特沃特
Atwater!
-趴下  -给我过来
- Stay down! - Get over here.
趴下
Stay down!
你还好吗
You all right?
-她失血太严重了  -我来吧
- She's bleeding pretty badly. - I got her.
我来吧  警官
I got her, officer.
你会没事的  亲爱的
You're gonna be all right, sweetheart, okay?
保持清醒  好吗
Stay with me. All right?
快走
Move.
你觉得你会忘记对这些女孩的所作所为吗
Hey. You think you're ever gonna forget what you did to those girls?
我向你保证这是绝对不可能的  柯林斯
I guarantee you that will not happen, Collins!
-艾琳  艾琳  别这样  -别担心
- Erin, Erin, come on. - Don't worry.
我保证这个人下场会很惨
I'll make sure this guy gets buried.
你听见他说的了  听见了吗
You hear that? Are you listening?
要想进我的部门  你们这样做就对了
Hey. That's the kind of effort that'll get you into my unit.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
警署见
I'll see you back at the district.
步步高升
Upstairs.
这就是我说的
That's what I'm talkin' about, girl.
你知道你这样做有多蠢吗
Hey. You know how stupid that was?
你在说什么
what are you talkin' about?
如果我们不进去  他们会把那女孩害死的
If we didn't go in there, they would've killed that girl.
顺便说一下  那250块有我的一半
You owe me half of that 250, by the way.
你一定在跟我开玩笑
You have got to be kidding me.
我可没在开玩笑
I ain't playin'.
不好意思
My bad.
好消息是没有人受伤  警长
Good news is no one was injured, Sergeant.
是还没有
Not yet.
艾琳
Erin.
贾斯汀在交管局里的主管给我打电话了
I got a call from Justin's supervisor at the CTA.
他说他压根就没出现
He said he never showed up.
是的  他之前去警署找过我
Yeah, he stopped by the district.
我不小心在健身房把他的钱包拿走了
I accidentally took his wallet from the gym.
是我的错
It's my bad.
我一直在监控我给他的那部电话
The cell I gave him, I've been monitoring it.
这个人和贾斯汀一起在斯泰茨维尔
He was in Statesville with Justin.
乔·卡塔拉诺  他有提起过他吗
Joe Catalano. He ever mention him?
没有  我会问问他的
No, I'll ask him.
我跟你说了要盯紧他
I told you to keep an eye on him.
听着  如果贾斯汀发现你暗中监视他
Listen, if Justin finds out that you're spying on him,
他只会跟你更加疏远
he's just gonna push you away farther.
我来处理这件事
I'll take care of this.
你回家吧
You go home.
我应该从逃生梯偷偷溜走吗
Should I sneak out the fire escape?
我要去先快速处理点事
I gotta go take care of something real quick.
谢谢你在这陪我
Thank you for being here.
今天真是漫长的一天
Today was a rough one.
你以前也这样陪过我
You've been there for me before.
我还是先等五分钟再走吧
I might wait like five minutes before I leave.
-当然  -好的
- Sure. - Yeah, all right.
你要干什么
What do you want?
我能进去吗
Can I come in?
我妈拒绝出席我的婚礼  意料之中
So my mom is refusing to come to the wedding, of course,
但她至少和我们一起挑选的蛋糕
but she at least came cake shopping with us.
我们选了榛子巧克力蛋糕
We went with chocolate hazelnut.
温迪非常想给你一块尝尝
Wendy really wanted you to have a piece.
好吧  那我们明天见吧
All right. Well, I'll see you tomorrow, I guess.
埃尔  你说得对
Al, you were right.
我是不应该一个人冲进去  我...
I shouldn't have rushed in there without you, and I'm--
我很抱歉
You know, I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我在你身上堵了一把你知道吗
You know, I took a chance on you, man.
每个  有些时候
Every--there-- there are moments
我觉得你会成为一位优秀的警察
when I think you could be a great cop.
其他时候
And other moments,
跟你共事就像是在俄罗斯轮盘中转枪膛似的
working with you is like spinning a cylinder in Russian roulette.
你可能是对的
You could be right,
但也有可能会因此付出生命代价
but you can be dead right.
你知道我想让你干什么吗
You know what I want you to do?
去密歇根大街干活或是找份其它轻松的工作
Go work Michigan Avenue or some other cushy assignment.
在害死我们俩前结婚并且退出警署
Get married, check out before you kill the both of us.
道森警探
Detective Dawson.
你好
Hi.
艾丽卡·格拉迪沙尔  内务部
Erica Gradishar. Internal Affairs.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我只是想正式介绍一下我自己
I just wanted to formally introduce myself
并且让你知道你有秘密后盾
and let you know you have a confidential place
任何时候你都可以来一吐为快
to come to if you ever need to get something off your chest.
你为什么认为我想找人谈谈
What makes you think I need to talk?
因为你是一位好警察
Because you're a good cop,
而且我讨厌看到好警察被坏警察给败坏了
and I hate to see a good cop tainted by a bad one.
跟他一样的
Whatever he's having.
上次我跟警察喝酒的时候
The last time I drank with a cop,
最后下场很惨
I wound up in county.
我知道这是怎么回事
I know how this works.
你在牢里照顾过贾斯汀
You looked out for Justin inside,
然后现在你觉得他欠你的
and now you think he owes you.
贾斯汀什么都不欠你的
Justin doesn't owe you anything.
你总不能因为和朋友出去玩而逮捕一个人吧
You can't arrest a guy for hanging out with his friends.
但我可以因为在你后备箱里
But I can arrest you for the 1/2 kilo
找到的半公斤毒品逮捕你
I'm gonna find in your trunk.